Test 1
Bài kiểm tra 1
Listening
Phần Nghe
Part 2
Phần 2
Listen and look
Nghe và nhìn
There is one example.
Có một ví dụ.
I was at a sports day last week.
Tuần trước tôi đã tham gia ngày hội thể thao.
Oh, was it at school?
Ồ, nó ở trường à?
No, it was at the sports centre.
Không, nó ở trung tâm thể thao.
The sports centre?
Trung tâm thể thao à?
Yes, that's right.
Vâng, đúng vậy.
Can you see the answer?
Bạn có thấy câu trả lời không?
Now you listen and write.
Bây giờ bạn nghe và viết.
What day was it on? Was it Monday?
Nó vào ngày nào? Thứ Hai à?
No, it was last Wednesday.
Không, thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right. Wednesday morning?
Đúng rồi. Sáng thứ Tư à?
No, after school.
Không, sau giờ học.
How many different kinds of sports were there?
Có bao nhiêu môn thể thao khác nhau?
I think there were eight.
Tôi nghĩ có tám môn.
Um, no, ten.
Ừm, không, mười.
Ten? That's a lot.
Mười à? Nhiều thật.
Yes, it is.
Vâng, đúng vậy.
What day was it on? Was it Monday?
Nó vào ngày nào? Thứ Hai à?
No, it was last Wednesday.
Không, thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right. It was last Wednesday.
Đúng rồi. Thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
Which is your favourite sport?
Môn thể thao yêu thích của bạn là gì?
I like basketball, but it's not my favourite.
Tôi thích bóng rổ, nhưng đó không phải môn yêu thích nhất.
My favourite is table tennis.
Môn yêu thích của tôi là bóng bàn.
Table tennis?
Bóng bàn à?
Yes, that's right.
Vâng, đúng vậy.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
What day was it on? Was it Monday?
Nó vào ngày nào? Thứ Hai à?
No, it was last Wednesday.
Không, thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
Did you have any food there?
Bạn có ăn gì ở đó không?
No, we had a picnic at City Park.
Không, chúng tôi đã đi dã ngoại ở Công viên City.
Centre Park?
Công viên Centre à?
No, City. C-I-T-Y.
Không, City. C-I-T-Y.
Oh yes, I know it.
Ồ vâng, tôi biết chỗ đó.
What day was it on? Was it Monday?
Nó vào ngày nào? Thứ Hai à?
No, it was last Wednesday.
Không, thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
What did you have to eat?
Bạn đã ăn gì?
I had my favourite food.
Tôi đã ăn món ăn yêu thích của tôi.
What's that? Ice cream?
Là gì vậy? Kem à?
Yes, that's right. Ice cream.
Vâng, đúng vậy. Kem.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
What day was it on? Was it Monday?
Nó vào ngày nào? Thứ Hai à?
No, it was last Wednesday.
Không, thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
Now listen to part 2 again.
Bây giờ hãy nghe lại phần 2.
What day was it on? Was it Monday?
Nó vào ngày nào? Thứ Hai à?
No, it was last Wednesday.
Không, thứ Tư tuần trước.
Right.
Đúng rồi.
Wednesday morning?
Sáng thứ Tư à?
No, after school.
Không, sau giờ học.
How many different kinds of sports were there?
Có bao nhiêu môn thể thao khác nhau?
I think there were 8.
Tôi nghĩ có 8 môn.
Um, no, 10.
Ừm, không, 10.
10? That's a lot.
10 à? Nhiều thật.
Yes, it is.
Vâng, đúng vậy.
Which is your favourite sport?
Môn thể thao yêu thích của bạn là gì?
I like basketball, but it's not my favourite.
Tôi thích bóng rổ, nhưng đó không phải môn yêu thích nhất.
My favourite is table tennis.
Môn yêu thích của tôi là bóng bàn.
Table tennis?
Bóng bàn à?
Yes, that's right.
Vâng, đúng vậy.
Did you have any food there?
Bạn có ăn gì ở đó không?
No, we had a picnic at City Park.
Không, chúng tôi đã đi dã ngoại ở Công viên City.
Centre Park?
Công viên Centre à?
No, City. C-I-T-Y.
Không, City. C-I-T-Y.
Oh yes, I know it.
Ồ vâng, tôi biết chỗ đó.
What did you have to eat?
Bạn đã ăn gì?
I had my favourite food.
Tôi đã ăn món ăn yêu thích của tôi.
What's that? Ice cream?
Là gì vậy? Kem à?
Yes, that's right. Ice cream.
Vâng, đúng vậy. Kem.
That is the end of part 2.
Đây là phần kết thúc của phần 2.